https://www.missioninn.com/policies-en.html

Policies | Mission Inn Riverside Hotel and Spa | Riverside CA
reservations
close
menu
close
ReservationsstayOffersdiningoverviewSunday BrunchDuane's Prime Steaks & SeafoodMission Inn RestaurantLas CampanasBella TrattoriaPresidential LoungeTHE CALIFORNIA LOUNGEdiningoverviewSunday BrunchDuane's Prime Steaks & SeafoodMission Inn RestaurantLas CampanasBella TrattoriaPresidential LoungeTHE CALIFORNIA LOUNGELas Campanas Tequila BarCasey’s cupcakesKellys SpaWeddings
reservations
rooms
from
$
199
.99
explore the mission inn
ReservationsstayOffersdiningoverviewSunday BrunchDuane's Prime Steaks & SeafoodMission Inn RestaurantLas CampanasBella TrattoriaPresidential LoungeTHE CALIFORNIA LOUNGEdiningoverviewSunday BrunchDuane's Prime Steaks & SeafoodMission Inn RestaurantLas CampanasBella TrattoriaPresidential LoungeTHE CALIFORNIA LOUNGELas Campanas Tequila BarCasey’s cupcakesKellys SpaWeddings
AboutAmenities & ServicesactivitiesMeetings & EventsphotosKelly's BoutiqueCasey's CupcakesFestival of LightsMap & DirectionsReservationsstayOffersdiningWeddingsKellys SpaAboutAmenities & ServicesMap & DirectionsactivitiesKelly's BoutiqueCasey's CupcakesphotosMeetings & EventsFestival of Lights
check availability
check-in date
nights
0102030405060708091011121314151617181920
guests
01020304050607080910
check rates
modify booking
For more information on our safety and wellbeing guidelines, please click here. Customers should review government guidance to confirm eligibility to travel and stay at the Mission Inn Hotel.
Best Rate Guarantee & Privacy Policy
Rest assured that you’ll always find the lowest rates for The Mission Inn Hotel & Spa on our official website . Feel confident when you book directly with us, knowing that you’re guaranteed the best available price for your stay.
If you do find a lower published rate prior to – or within 24 hours of – booking your hotel room or suite, please give us a call. We’ll happily honor that confirmed lower rate.
Note that our Best Rate Guarantee does not include packaged rates or reservations booked via opaque or auction sites.
Privacy Policy
The Mission Inn Hotel & Spa is committed to providing quality information and services to the community. In order to do this, we need to know a little about you. The web site is hosted in the U.S. and on content distribution servers worldwide.
WHAT INFORMATION DO WE COLLECT?
We collect only the domain name, but not the e-mail address of visitors to our web pages. We also collect aggregate and user-specific information on the pages consumers’ access or visit. The information we gather is used for internal review to improve the content of our web pages. It is not sold or traded with other organizations for commercial purposes.
COOKIES
We use cookies to record session information and to track a user's path through our websites. This enables us to respond to any problems with our service and offer more personalized care.
YOUR PRIVACY IS IMPORTANT TO US
We strive to do everything we can to protect the privacy of our users. We do not sell or exchange personally identifiable information with any third parties.
From time to time, we may utilize customer information for new, unanticipated uses not previously disclosed in our privacy notice. If our information practices change at some time in the future, we will post the policy changes on our website to notify you of these revisions and provide you with the ability to opt out of these new uses.
If you are concerned about how your information is used, we recommend that you review this Privacy Statement periodically as the Mission Inn Hotel & Spa may update it from time to time.
If you feel that this site is not following its stated information policy, you can contact our IS department. We will be sure to address your concerns.
read more
read less
explore
awardscontactpress roomGift CardscareersactivitiesStay Connected
Sign up to be the first to learn about special packages, promotional offers and exclusive events in our monthly e-news.
sign up
awardscontactpress roomGift CardscareersactivitiesStay Connectedbest rate guarantee/PrivacyAccessibility Noticesitemap
Designed by TravelClick
copyright
© 2020
the mission inn hotel & spa
